When you are selecting a teapot that is glass, it is always best to go with the best brand because glass already is very fragile.
So, you want to buy something that can withstand the heat without worrying about pouring warm water in there, prepare the teapot.
This is a Yana glass teapot.
This teapot is amazing.
You can put it in boiling water and then put it in the freezer and it will not break.
It is also handmade, where the spout, when you pour the tea, it is a drip-less spout.
You will know what I mean in just a second.
This is the best type of teapot if you are trying to brew a white tea or a very nice green tea, and you like to see the color of the brew and you like to see the leaves dance.
This is the filter that you put in, and you would put your tea leaves in here as such.
I am using my hands but I recommend using a teaspoon, unless you are making it for yourself.
And then, you put your hot water in.
Once you do that, the teas would rise and you will be able to see the color of the tea.
Mind you, I am not worried about the fact that I am putting boiling water in a cold pot.
And, you can see the color changed with time.
Can the camera catch this?
You can see all the actions of the tea leaves, whereas with other teapots, the teas are brewing and the only thing you see is what goes into a cup.
And, the flowering tea will bloom.
And, for flowering tea, you do not necessarily need to use a tea filter.
All you need to use, is put the hot water in, and then you put your tea flower in and it will bloom and take up the whole pot.
And, this will be a wonderful display when you have guests over.
And, what I mean by this drip-less teapot is so.
Do you notice that?
Great pot if you like to see your teas, and as well as be able to drink tea when it is a little bit cooler.